바나나땅콩 머핀이
딱 하나 남았어
Chandler, Mon, there's only one
banana-nut muffin left.
I ordered mine first.
내가 먼저 시켰잖아
Yeah, but I'm so much faster.
내 손이 더 빨랐어
Give it to me.
- 이리 내
- 싫어
No.
이리 내!
Give it to me!
알았어, 너 먹어
Okay, you can have it.
There you go. Enjoy your coffee.
커피 맛있게 마셔
내가 오기 전에
딴 사람이 마신 거야
That was there when I got here.
누가 뉴욕에 오는지
한번 맞춰 봐
Hey, you'll never guess
who's coming to New York.
삼키기 전에 얼른 말해
Quick, tell us before he swallows.
알았어, 나랑 사귀었던
해군이 온대
Ryan, that guy I dated
who's in the Navy.
You went out with a guy in the Navy?
해군이랑 사귀었어?
워싱턴 공원에서
노래부르다 만났는데
I met him while playing guitar
in the park.
Ryan threw in saltwater taffy
because he didn't have change.
라이언이 동전이 없다고
소금물 사탕을 넣었었어
'소금물 사탕 남자'를
그 때 작곡한 거야?
Is that when you wrote
"Saltwater Taffy Man"?
아니
잠수함 승무원이라서
2년에 한 번씩 오면
No, he's my submarine guy.
He resurfaces every couple years...
사흘 간 나와 환상적인
시간을 보냈는데
...and we have an amazing
three days together.
Only this time, he's coming for 2 weeks.
Two whole weeks, which means "yea"!
이번엔 2주 동안 나온대
2주 내내 함께할 거라고!
한 번에 2년씩이나
잠수한다고?
So this guy goes down
for, like, two years at a time?
내 머핀을 핥은 죗값이다
That'll teach you to lick my muffin.
Hi.
안녕
왜 그래?
Oh, no. What happened?
캐롤에게 전화 왔는데
벤이 수두에 걸렸대
I just spoke to Carol.
Ben's got chickenpox.
저런!
Oh, no.
Yeah, so if you haven't had it,
chances are you'll get it.
수두를 안 앓았던 사람은
전염될 거야
-I've had it.
- 난 수두 했었어
- 나도
-Had it.
나만 소외감 느껴지네
이것 봐!
I've never had it. I feel so left out.
Oh, look!
The One With the Chicken Pox
또 침대 정리를 했어요?
그럴 필요 없다니까
Honey, you made the bed again.
I told you, you don't have to do that.
This isn't camp.
애들 캠프도 아니고
어젯밤의 팬티 단속은
괜한 것이었군
Then I guess the panty raid last night
was totally uncalled for.
오늘은 샤워하며 짐 크로치의
'리로이 브라운'을 부를 거야
I'm taking a shower. Today I'll
sing Jim Croce's "Leroy Brown."
모니카!
물어 볼 게 있는데
Hey, Mon, I have a question.
리로이가 최고의 악당이야
아니면 최고의 뚱보야?
Is Leroy the baddest man
in the whole damn town...
...or the fattest man?
The baddest. Otherwise, the song
would be "Fat, Fat Leroy Brown."
악당이요
아님 가사가 '뚱보 브라운'
이랬겠죠
뭐 하는 거야?
What are you doing?
당신 기다리고 있었죠
I'm just waiting for you, sweetie.
침대 다시 정리해?
Are you remaking the bed?
미안해요, 당신이 한 것도
괜찮았어요
I'm sorry. The way you did it,
it was just fine.
그럼 왜 뒤집어 엎어?
Then you're redoing it
because...?
You'll think I'm crazy.
말하면 내가 미친 줄 알걸요?
안 해도 마찬가지야
You're pretty much
running that risk either way.
Okay. You see...
알았어요
...the duvet tag shouldn't be
at the top left corner...
이불 상표는 왼쪽 위가 아니라
오른쪽 아래에 있어야 해요
...it should be at the
bottom right corner.
- 미친 정도는 아닌데
- 시작에 불과해요
-That's not so crazy.
-I'm just easing you in.
알았어
All right.
You see these little flower blossoms?
이 꽃들 보이죠?
엎어놓으면 안 된다고요
They should be facing up not down...
...because the head of the bed
is where the sun would be.
머리맡이 태양이 있는
방향이니까요
You don't love me anymore, do you?
이제 나 사랑하지 않죠?
Actually, if it's possible,
I love you more.
믿을지 모르겠지만
더 사랑하는 것 같아
Really?
정말로요?
Wow. Well, then, come on!
그럼 따라와요!
휴지 접는 방법을 알려 주죠
I wanna show you how to fold
the toilet paper into a point.
If you need something
to hold you over...
조이, 직장이 필요하다면
초급 전산원으로 채용할게
...I can get you a job here
as an entry-level processor.
- 경험이 필요하지 않아?
- 금방 배워
Don't you need experience?
It's not hard to learn.
As for people realizing you don't know
what you're doing, you're an actor.
사람들이 네가 엉망이라고
생각해도
넌 배우잖아
대충 잘하는 척만 하면
Act like a processor,
people will think you're a processor.
진짜 전산원으로 알 거라고
오전 계획안이에요
Here's this morning's projections.
고마워요, 스캇
이쪽은 조이 트리비아니
Thanks.
Scott Alexander, Joey Tribbiani.
조이는 전산원이에요
Joey is a fellow processor.
정말이에요?
No kidding?
그럼요
I process. People want the processing,
I'm the one they call.
전산 일이 필요하면
다들 내게 연락을 하죠
- 어디서 근무해요?
- 요즘은 여러 일을 해요
-Where do you work?
-Well, I'm in between things.
You know, one day you're processing,
the next day...
하루는 전산 일을 하고
다음 날은 다른 일 하고
...you're not so much
processing anymore.
조이에게 플레쉬맨 그룹의
공석을 맡기려고요
I told Joey about the opening
in Fleischman's group.
Fleischman's group.
플레쉬맨 그룹이라...
Whatever you do,
don't touch his sandwiches.
그 사람 샌드위치만
안 건드리면 괜찮을 거예요
전산원들 다 저래?
Are all you processors dorks?
This lipstick looks just great on you.
립스틱이 정말 잘 어울려
정말 예뻐
You look fabulous.
You really do.
Yeah, are you sure?
Really?
정말이야?
See, you look beautiful.
For God sakes, dim the lights.
눈이 부실 정도로 예뻐
조명 낮춰
마녀 같잖아!
I'm hideous!
괜찮을 거야
라이언은 물 속에만 있었다면?
It's gonna be okay.
Ryan's been underwater.
He's just gonna be glad you don't
have barnacles on your butt.
곰보만 아니면
괜찮다고 할 거라고
Come in.
들어와요
Hey, baby, I'm back
나 왔어, 자기
어서 와, 라이언
Hey, Ryan. What's up?
왜 그래?
What's going on?
안 돼, 물러서 있어
발진이 났거든
No, no.
You have to stay back.
I have the pox!
수두, 아니면 천연두?
Chicken or small?
수두야, 채식만 했는데
막을 수가 없었어
Chicken, which is so ironic
considering I'm a vegetarian.
-Why aren't you home in bed?
-My grandmother's never had chickenpox.
- 집에 누워 있지 그랬어
- 할머니께 옮길까 봐
Please tell me you have, because
oh, my God, I forgot how cute you are.
넌 수두 앓았었겠지?
네 잘생긴 얼굴을 잊어버렸어
I'm sorry, I never had them.
나도 안 했어
If I had one wish,
I'd go back to when I was 7...
한 가지 소원을 빌 수 있다면
지미가 수두를 앓았던
7살 때로 돌아가서
...when Jimmy Hauser had chickenpox,
and rub that kid all over my face.
그 녀석 얼굴에 비벼대겠어
아님 내가 수두 안 걸리길
빌어도 되고
Yeah, or you could wish
that I didn't have them now.
얼굴 좀 보여 줘
Can I see your face?
안 돼!
No. You don't wanna see a face
covered with pox.
수두에 걸린 얼굴을 보면
역겨울 거야
훈제연어를 뒤집어썼대도
상관없어
It could be lox, I wouldn't care.
And you hate fish.
참, 넌 생선 싫어하지
고맙기도 해라
알았어, 보여 줄게
So sweet. All right.
Okay, all right.
You can see.
이게 내 모습이야
This is me.
미안해!
Sorry!
I am scary!
난 마녀야!
하필 그 때 천둥이 쳐서
잠깐 놀란 거야
The lightening was
an unfortunate coincidence.
너무 예뻐!
예뻐 죽겠다고!
You look lovely!
Lovely!
화나 죽겠어
I hate this.
함께 멋진 2주를 계획했는데
I had the most amazing
two weeks planned for us.
And everything I had in mind,
we had to be a lot closer than this.
이렇게 떨어져서는
아무것도 못하잖아
I've spent the last eight months
in a steel tube with men...
지난 8개월 간 철통에서
남자들과 생활하면서
...thinking about this moment.
이 순간만을 기다려 왔어
그런 발진 몇 개 때문에
망칠 수는 없어
I am not gonna let a bunch...
...of itchy spots stand between us.
이렇게 낭만적인 병은
처음인 것 같아
Okay. This is the most
romantic disease I've ever had.
-How's the first day?
-Good. It's like you said.
- 첫 출근 어때?
- 좋아, 네 말이 맞았어
칼럼에 숫자만 쳐 넣으면
되는 일이더라고
It's putting numbers
from one column into another.
There you go.
다행이군
사람들도 좋아
And everybody's nice. I just had
a good talk with that lady Jeannie.
빨강머리 지니와 얘기했는데
Jeannie? The head of
East Coast operations, Jeannie?
- 동부지역 담당 지니 말이야?
- 그래
알고 보니 우리 아이들이
같은 학교에 다니더라고
Turns out our kids go
to the same school.
Yeah. Small world, huh?
세상 참 좁지?
이상한 세상이네
Weird world.
Your kids?
자식이 있어?
I figure my character has kids.
내 인물에 자식이 있다고
설정했거든
지금 한 말에 대한
해설판 나오니?
There isn't a part of that sentence
I don't need explained.
연기를 할 때는
모든 상황을 생각해야 돼
When you're acting, you need
to think about that stuff.
내 인물인 전산원 조셉은
My character,
Joseph the processing guy...
애슐리와 브리트니라는
두 딸이 있어
... has two little girls,
Ashley and Brittany.
Ashley copies everything
Brittany does.
애슐리는 뭐든
브리트니를 흉내내지
투명인간 아이들이
뭘 못하겠어?
Well, invisible kids
can be that way sometimes.
조셉과 아내 캐런은
셋째를 계획 중이야
You know, Joseph and his wife, Karen,
are thinking of having a third kid.
You know what?
이거 알아?
벌써 가졌어
Just did.
네 가공의 정자 파워가
엄청나구나
That's some pretty powerful
imaginary sperm you must have there.
IKnow what makes the itching worse?
왜 더 가려운지 알아?
계속 그 얘기만 해대서?
That you don't stop talking about it?
-Fine.
-Let's just play, okay?
- 알았어
- 게임이나 계속하자고
Good, okay.
좋아
6이 두 개 나오면...
Here we go, double sixes.
Here we go....
엄마 말 들어야지
내가 주사위 굴리면...
Here we go....
Come to Mama.
Getting ready to roll the dice....
What are you doing?
Are you scratching?
뭐야?
지금 긁는 거야?
아니, 행운을 비는 거야
No. This is what I do
for luck, okay?
긁고 있잖아
You're scratching.
- 주사위 이리 내
- 싫어!
Give me the dice.
- 주사위 이리 내!
- 굴렸어!
-Give me the dice.
-No! Here. There!
더블 6이야!
Look, double sixes!
긁으면 흉터가 남는다고
We can't scratch. We'll scar.
I can't stop thinking about it.
It's just so hard.
자꾸 그 생각만 나
너무 힘들어
I wanna grab these houses
and rub them all over my body.
이 집들을 내 몸에다
비벼댔으면 좋겠어!
-No!
-Give it!
- 안 돼!
- 이 손 놔!
Come on!
You know you want it.
You know you want it too.
자기도 이러고 싶잖아!
Let's just be bad.
It'll feel so good.
우리 서로 긁어 주자
기분이 좋아지잖아
Come on.
어서....
Oh, God, help me.
- 오, 주여!
- 좋지?
-Oh, yeah.
-Okay, good. Now do me.
- 아주 좋아
- 이번엔 날 긁어 줘
Do my back.
Oh, come on. Harder!
등을 긁어 줘
더 세게!
There you go.
- 움직이지 마
- 왜?
-Don't move.
-Why?
-What are you...?
어떻게 하려고?
너무 좋아!
당장 그만둬!
Stop that.
Stop that right now.
피비 넌 이해하겠지만
I might've expected this of Phoebe.
But, Ryan, you're a military man.
라이언, 군인의 신분을
망각하지 말아요!
You and Milton have to join us
on the boat. Bring the kids.
부군과 함께 보트 타러 가요
아이들도 데려오고
하루 멋지게 보내자고요
We'll make a day of it.
그럼 좋죠
언제 날 한번 잡아요
That sounds lovely.
We'll have to set it up.
I better get back.
Hope the baby feels better.
난 그만 가야겠어요
아기가 빨리 나아야 할 텐데
고마워요
잘 가요, 지니
Thanks.
-Bye-bye, Jeannie.
-Bye-bye, Joseph.
What a phony.
연기 끝내주지?
You'll teach her a lesson when she
steps off the dock onto nothing.
바닷물에 빠져 보면
뭔가 깨닫겠지
-Hey, Mr. Douglas.
-Sir.
안녕하세요, 사장님
빙, 메모 받았는데 보고서가
다음 금요일에나 된다고?
Bing, I got your memo. We're not gonna
see the report until next Friday?
팀원들이 가족들과
주말을 보내고 싶어해서요
My group wants to spend
the holiday with family.
나도 가족은 있지만
출근한다고
I have a family.
I'm gonna be here.
설명해 봐, 빙
Yeah, Bing.
What's that about?
사기진작을 위해서
쉬게 해주려는 겁니다
It's about cutting them
a little slack for morale.
대충 한다면 수요일까지
끝낼 수도 있습니다
Look, I can get some
rough numbers by Wednesday.
대충 한다고?
Rough numbers?
이 회사는 대충 만들어진
회사가 아니죠
This company wasn't built
on rough numbers. Right, Mr. Douglas?
안 그렇습니까, 사장님?
Have the final numbers
on my desk by Tuesday.
화요일까지 내 책상에
최종 보고서를 올려놓게
If you say so, sir.
알겠습니다
조셉 연기 뛰어나지?
Joseph's good, isn't he?
넌 내 손에 죽었어
I'm going to kill you.
조셉을 덜렁이로 설정했거든
Hey, I just figured Joseph's
the kind of guy who likes to mix it up.
아무 데나 끼여서
천방지축 날뛰는 거지
You know, get in there,
ruffle some feathers.
왜?
Why?
Look, I'm sorry,
but that's what Joseph does.
미안하지만 원래 조셉이
그런 걸 어떡해?
Okay? If you try to pull something...
네가 뭔 일을 하려면
조셉이 먼저 물을 거야
... he'll call you on it.
'뭘 하려는 거지?' 하면서
"What are you trying to pull?"
he'll say.
Duct tape.
은박 테이프!
Was I supposed to bring something too?
나도 뭘 갖고 왔어야 했나?
이걸로 친구들 손에다
오븐 장갑을 붙였어요
This is for the scratchy twins.
I taped oven mitts to their hands.
You're strict.
- 엄격하군
- 친구들을 위해서죠
Well, it's for their own good.
You know, I like the way you have
efficiently folded this tab under.
테이프를 붙여 놓다니
정말 마음이 놓이네
See, in a tape emergency you could
shave valuable seconds off your time.
긴급상황에서 천금같은
시간을 아낄 수 있잖아
Exactly!
맞아요!
당신 옆에서 까탈대도
괜찮아서 너무 좋아요!
God, I love that I can be
totally neurotic around you now.
Tell me the truth.
솔직히 말해 봐요
Don't you like having everything
on your desk perpendicular?
책상 위의 물건들의 줄을
일렬로 맞추니까 좋죠?
각도가 안 맞으면
절대 안 되지
If it's not a right angle,
it is a wrong angle.
- 바로 그거예요
- 고마워
-Very good.
-Thank you.
Tomorrow, I'm gonna do your clocks.
내일은 벽시계를 해줄게요
벽시계를 어쩌려고?
You're gonna do what to my clocks?
Set them to my time.
내 시간에 맞추는 거죠
I'm confused.
좀 혼란스럽군
우리 시간을 나눈 게 아니었나?
I thought we shared time.
난 침실 시계를 6분 빠르게
해놓거든요, 왜 그런지 알아요?
No. See, in my bedroom
I set my clock six minutes fast.
Wanna know why?
Because it's in a slightly different
time zone than the kitchen?
부엌 시계랑 안 맞아서?
Forget it.
- 관둬요
- 아냐, 말해 줘
No, come on, tell me.
-You don't understand.
-Come on.
- 이해를 못하잖아요
- 어서 말해
당신은 그 무엇에도
집착하지 않잖아요
You don't have any obsessive things.
No, that's not true.
그렇지 않아
Oh, yeah?
Tell me one of yours.
그래요?
그럼 뭐에 집착하죠?
좋아
One of my things is
I always separate my sweat socks...
난 항상 운동화 양말을
구두 양말과 구분해 놓지
...from my dress socks.
- 섞이면요?
- 그럴 경우엔...
What if they get mixed up?
Boy, I would just....
I would freak out.
머리가 돌아버리지
You would not.
거짓말!
I can't believe this.
I hate this. You're too normal.
당신은 믿을 수 없을 정도로
너무 정상이에요!
내 애인이 집착을 않다니
I can't believe you
don't have a "thing."
My boyfriend doesn't have a "thing."
집착을 안 한다니!
누가 들었으면
나라곤 생각 못할 거야
See, if anyone overheard that,
I didn't come off well.
사장님이 널 찾아
-Mr. Douglas is looking for you.
-Why is Mr. Douglas looking for me?
사장님이 왜 날 찾아?
He suspects you dropped the ball
on the Lender project.
네가 렌더 프로젝트를
망쳤다고 생각하거든
왜 그렇게 생각하지?
Why? Why does he suspect that?
At first, he thought it was Joseph...
처음엔 조셉이라 생각하고
그에게 물어 봤는데
...but after he asked Joseph about it,
turns out it was you.
너라는 결론이 나왔거든
-Anyway, I thought you should know.
-All right. That's it.
- 알고 있는 게 좋을 듯해서
- 더는 못 참아!
조이, 네가 이 연기를
즐기는 건 알지만
Look, Joey...
... I realize this is the role
of a lifetime for you...
...and if I could just fire Joseph,
I would. But that's not possible.
조셉을 해고하고 싶은데
그게 불가능하니까
So I have to let you both go.
너희 둘 다 해고하겠어
뭔 소리야?
모두가 조셉을 좋아하는데
What? Everybody loves Joseph.
난 아냐
조셉을 아주 싫어한다고
I don't. I hate Joseph.
아주 싸가지가 없는
녀석이거든
I think he's a brown-nosing suck-up.
조셉을 해고할 순 없어
네 부서원도 아니잖아
You can't fire Joseph.
He's not in your department.
All right, okay.
So I can't fire Joseph...
좋아, 좋다고
조셉을 해고하지 못하면...
... but I can sleep with his wife.
그놈 부인과 자겠어
Not Karen!
캐런은 안 돼!
그녀와 바람 피우려고 해
Yeah, I'm thinking about
having an affair with her.
이거 알아?
You know what?
방금 잤어!
I just did.
What the hell are you doing?
지금 무슨 짓이야?
Oh, it's not me.
내가 아냐
내가 맡은 인물이지
It's my character!
챈디라고!
Chandie.
The rogue processor who seduces
his coworkers' wives...
동료의 아내들을 유혹하는
껄렁한 전산원이라고
...and then laughs about it.
지금 내 책상 서랍에
그녀의 팬티가 있어!
In fact, I have her panties
right there in my drawer!
-Really?
-No, freak show, she's fictional!
- 정말?
- 아니, 이건 허구잖아!
진정해!
Take it easy.
If it means that much to you,
I'll go find something else.
네가 그렇게 생각한다면
다른 일을 찾아볼게
Thank you.
고마워
It's just that
I'm gonna miss Joseph.
난 조셉이 그리울 거야
I liked him. His wife.
조셉 내외를 좋아했거든
화끈한 여자였어
She was hot.
제발 이것 좀 벗겨 줘
정말 안 긁을게
Please take these off.
I swear I won't scratch.
미안, 모니카의 명령이거든
No, sorry, hon.
Monica's orders.
정말 힘드네
Well, that wasn't easy.
저녁 다됐어
Okay, dinner's on.
There's a peach cobbler
warming in the oven.
오븐엔 복숭아 파이가 있어
So the plate's gonna be hot, but that
shouldn't be a problem for you.
접시가 뜨겁지만
너희는 데지 않을 거야
All right, you kids.
Bye, now.
우리는 갈게
-Bye.
-Oh, look, look.
- 안녕
- 저것 좀 봐
저예산 인형극이야
A low-budget puppet show.
A shame you can't see
what finger I'm holding up.
내 손가락 모양을 못 봐서
정말 유감이야
알았어
- 와인 줄까?
- 응
-Wine?
-Please.
- 좀 흘렸네
- 내가 치울게
-Spilled some.
-I got it.
You look beautiful tonight.
자기 오늘 너무 아름다워
What?
- 뭐라고?
- 미안해
Sorry.
자기 아름다워
You look beautiful.
더 이상은 못 참아!
You know what? That's it.
That's it.
Oh, yes.
Good.
좋아...
혹시...
You guys, did you?
Monica...
모니카, 어서 일어나
...wake up.
What's up?
- 왜요?
- 한 가지 생각해 냈어
I thought of a thing.
Yeah?
- 그래요?
- 그래
I have to sleep, have to,
on this side of the bed.
난 반드시 오른쪽에서
잠을 자야 해
그야 당연하죠
No. You have to sleep
on this side of the bed...
자기가 오른쪽에서 자는 이유는
... because I have to sleep
on this side of the bed.
내가 반드시 왼쪽에서
자기 때문이에요
나한테 속은 건 아닐까?
Or so I would have you believe.
모두가 한쪽에서만 자는
버릇이 있잖아요
So you have a side of the bed.
Everybody has a side of the bed.
Hey, come on. You haven't
heard my reason yet.
이유도 안 들어 봤잖아
All right, go on.
말해 봐요
난 캘리포니아에서 자라서
반드시 서쪽에서 자야 해
I have to sleep on the west side...
... because I grew up in California...
...and otherwise...
아님 바다의 위치가
바뀐 거잖아
...the ocean would be on the wrong side.
맙소사
자기 정말 미쳤어!
Oh, my God.
You're a freak!
내가 그랬잖아
How about that?
이번엔 어디로 항해하죠?
Where're you shipping off to?
I really can't say.
기밀입니다
잠수함에 핵무기도
탑재했어요?
Do you have nuclear weapons onboard?
기밀입니다
I can't say.
그 잠망경으로 밖을
내다봐요?
Do you get to look through
a periscope thingy?
미안하지만 말 못합니다
I'm sorry, but I can't say.
잠수함에 대해 배우니
정말 좋네요
Wow, it's neat learning
about submarines.
- 비행기 시간이 돼서
- 내가 바래다 줄게
-I better not miss my flight.
-I'll walk you out.
- 잘 가요, 라이언
- 만나서 반가웠어요
-Bye, Ryan.
-Pleasure. Take care.
자기도 저런 유니폼을
입으면 어떨까?
So do you think we could get you
one of those uniform things?
- 제복이 좋아?
- 그럼
You like that, do you?
Oh, yeah.
- 전화하고 올게
- 알았어
I'll make some calls.
그렇게 2주를 보내다니
믿어지질 않아
Can you believe that's how
we spent our two weeks?
전혀 낭만적이지 않았잖아
We didn't do the romantic
things I'd planned...
센트럴 파크에 소풍도 못 가고
대신 센트럴 퍼크에서...
...Iike having a picnic in Central Park
and coffee at Central Perk.
이게 그 뜻이었구나!
Oh, I just got that!
택시!
Taxi!
Bye, you.
안녕, 자기
I'm sorry, we're
오늘 영업...
- 어서 와요, 선장님
- 원하는 게 이거였어?
Hey, sailor.
Is this what you had in mind?
I'll say.
그런 것 같아
I'm shipping out tomorrow.
내일 출항하는데
Well, then...
그럼 잊지 못할 밤을
보내야지
...we better make this night count.
잠깐, 카푸치노 기계를 안 껐어
Wait, I forgot to turn off
the cappuccino machine.
닻을 올려라!
Anchors aweigh.
Oh, wait, wait!
My purse, my purse!
잠깐만, 내 지갑!
I forgot to turn off the bathroom light.
참, 화장실 불을 안 껐어
나중에 집에서 봐
Why don't I just meet you upstairs?
로스!
Honey!